

SQL DEVELOPER

Details

Pune

India

+ 91 7559211185

mitalipardeshi00@gmail.com

01		
W	7	lls
no 1	V III	

SQL

T-SQL

PL/SOL

Microsoft Azure

SSIS

ETL

Microsoft Excel

Languages

English

Hindi

Marathi

Profile

As a committed and hardworking individual with a work experience of 1.5 years, I strive to excel in everything I do. I am dedicated to continuously learning and growing both personally and professionally. With a track record of success, I possess the drive and leadership skills to achieve any goal set before me.

Employment History

Survey Programming Analyst, Annalect India, Andheri

DECEMBER 2022 - MARCH 2023

Hands on experience in writing complex SQL queries, Procedure, function and triggers.

Worked on SQL database creation for Healthcare projects for USA and UK clients and took full responsibility of survey programming.

Performed ETL to merge multiple survey databases that was required for analytics and data mining purpose.

Modified T-SQL procedures to account for added columns in Azure SQL Cloud Database.

Examined existing SQL queries and made performance improvements by removing unnecessary query nesting.

Associate Analyst(Survey Programmer), Ugam Solutions Pvt. Ltd., Thane

NOVEMBER 2021 - NOVEMBER 2022

Communicate with clients and solved their queries on live projects.

Worked on creating database structure based on the information provided by the client (Hall And Partners), including survey programming, setting filters and quotas, managing languages, translations, exporting and reporting

Imported database and merged data into excel from multiple databases for further analysis.

Worked on JavaScript, HTML, CSS to implement survey logic(segmentation, max-diff, Light Box setup, Audio to text Converter) and improve UI and UX of survey.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science (BCS), Bhonsala Military College, Nashik

JUNE 2018 - APRIL 2021

Graduated with distinction - 73%

College projects:

MySQL database for E-Commerce Website(2nd Year)

E-Commerce Website for women's clothes(3rd Year)

Courses

Front end development - CSS

HTML Attributes and Tags

Programming Basics

Software Testing Fundamentals

Automation Testing (Selenium)